Nature judges like a god all men that come to her.
Butcher's Crossing is a western, drama film directed by Gabe Polsky.
In the 1870s, a young Harvard dropout seeks his destiny out West by tying his
fate to a team of buffalo hunters led by a man named Miller.
Together, they embark on a harrowing journey risking life and sanity.
Miller, played by Nicolas Cage.
Will Andrews, played by Fred Hechinger.
Fred Schneider, played by Jeremy Bobb.
McDonald, played by Paul Raci.
Charlie Hoge, played by Xander Berkeley.
Francine, played by Rachel Keller.
Butcher's Crossing is a 2023 American Western film directed by Gabe Polsky in his
narrative feature film debut, based on the 1960 novel by John Edward Williams.
It stars Nicolas Cage, Fred Hechinger, Xander Berkeley,
Rachel Keller, Jeremy Bobb, and Paul Raci.
It had its world premiere at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 9, 2022
and was released in the United States on October 20, 2023 by Saban Films.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
buffalo, american west, 1870s, college dropout.
The tone is emotional.